A Guide to the the Student Council Office Administrative Files, 1972-1995
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Student Council Office Administrative Files 1972-1995
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/4.961
This collection consists of 15,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred in 1996 September.
Scope and Content Information
The papers consist of topical files including those issues addressed by the Student Council on Women's Concerns and Gay and Lesbian Concerns.
Organization
Series I: Topical Files, 1972-1995
Series II: Women's Concerns, 1972-1994
Series III: Gay and Lesbian Concerns, 1972-1993
Series IV: Restricted Materials, 1978-1995
Contents List
- Topical Files
  - ACC Leadership Conference 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Activities Coordinating Committee 1984 (Box 1)
  - Addresses and Phone Numbers 1987-1990 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Committee 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - African-American Students at the University of Virginia 1991 (Box 1)
  - Agenda and Minutes--Student Council 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Agenda and Minutes--Student Council 1992 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol Awareness Committee 1983 (Box 1)
  - Allocations Release Letters 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association Scholarship--Student Council Committee 1983 (Box 1)
  - Alumni-Student Cooperative (TASC) 1980-1984 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS) 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS) 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS) 1986-1989 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations 1984 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations Appeals 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations Committee--Allocations 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - Appropriations Committee--General 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Area Requirements--College of Arts and Sciences 1989 (Box 2)
  - Arts and Sciences Alumni Council 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Athletics 1983-1985 (Box 2)
  - Attendance 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Attendance 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Attendance 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Attendance 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Attendance 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Attendance Books 1981-1985 (Box 2)
  - Auxiliary Services Evaluation of Growth Potential 1989 (Box 2)
  - Bicycle Survey 1987-1990 (Box 2)
  - Black American Law Student Association 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Black Concerns--Coordinator 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Black Concerns--Weekly Meetings 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Black Faculty Recruitment ant Retention at the University of Virginia 1981-1985 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors 1986-1988 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors 1990 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors--Guidelines for Allocating Funds 1973-1980 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors--Student Member Selections 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Book Exchange--Publicity 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Book Exchange--Student Council 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Book Exchange--Tax Status 1974 (Box 3)
  - Book Exchange--Year End Reports 1984-1992 (Box 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1980 (Box 3)
  - Bus Hours Survey 1989 (Box 3)
  - Bylaws and Guidelines 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - Bylaws and Proposed Changes 1991 (Box 3)
  - Calendar Committee 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Cavalier Catering 1990 (Box 4)
  - Club Sports Address and Phone 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Committee Chairmen/Vice-chairmen Applications 1988 (Box 4)
  - Committee Expenditure Reports 1985-1989, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Committee Expense Reports 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Independence for Students with Disabilities 1991 (Box 4)
  - Committee on Residential Life (CORL) 1982 (Box 5)
  - Committee Progress Reports 1984-1987 (Box 5)
  - Committee to Review the Area Requirements--Final Report 1991 (Box 5)
  - Committees 1989 (Box 5)
  - Community Concerns 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Community Concerns 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Community Concerns 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - Community Relations Board 1991-1992 (Box 5)
  - Community Resource Assistant (CRA) 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Conferences 1987-1988 (Box 5)
  - Contracted Independent Organizations (CIO) 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Correspondence 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence--Andre Morgan 1990-1992 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--David Savage, Vice President for Student Organizations 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--John Sperling, Vice President for Issues 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--Lee Barnes 1989 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--Miscellaneous 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--Officers 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence--Ron Hohauser, Student Council President 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB) 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB) Draft 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Anthropology 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Art 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Astronomy 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Biology 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Chemistry 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Classics (Greek and Latin) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Drama 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Economics 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Engineering: Computer Science and Applied Mathematics 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--English 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Environmental Sciences 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Evaluation Forms 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--German 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Government and Foreign Affairs 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--History 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Master Lists 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Mathematics 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Miscellaneous Languages (Arabic, Chinese, Japanese, Swedish, Italian) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Music 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Philosophy 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Physics 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Psychology 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Religious Studies 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Rhetoric and Communication Studies (RCS) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Russian 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Sign-out Sheets n.d. (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Sociology 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Spanish 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Staff Positions and Applications n.d. (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB)--Survey Forms 1985-1987 (Box 8)
  - Course Evaluation Book (CEB) and Hook Book Orders 1989 (Box 8)
  - Credit Union 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - C.R.O.P. 1983 (Box 9)
  - Curriculum Requirements 1989 (Box 9)
  - Dean of Students 1981-1983 (Box 9)
  - Dean of Students 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - Department of Education and Student Council of Higher Education 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Dining Services n.d. (Box 9)
  - Dining Services 1984-1989 (Box 9)
  - Dining Services 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Dining Services 1992 (Box 9)
  - Dining Services Advisory Committee 1989 (Box 10)
  - Dining Services--Alternatives to Contract n.d. (Box 10)
  - Dining Services--Client Report 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Dining Services 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Dining Services--Renovation Committee 1989 (Box 10)
  - Dining Services--Survey and Assessment 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Draft Registration Legislation 1985 (Box 10)
  - Drinking 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Drug Free Resolution 1989 (Box 10)
  - Drunk Driving Legislation 1985 (Box 10)
  - Education Budget Cuts 1982-1984 (Box 10)
  - Education Legislation 1985 (Box 10)
  - Enrollment Growth at the University of Virginia 1989 (Box 10)
  - Environmental Issues 1989 (Box 10)
  - Escort Service 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - Escort Service 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Escort Service Committee and Handbook 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Escort Service Log 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Ethnic Concerns 1993 (Box 11)
  - Evaluation Book--Virginia Tech 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Expansion (Report to Board of Visitors--BOV) 1989-1990 (Box 11)
  - Expenditure Procedures n.d. (Box 11)
  - Expenditure Reports 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Expenditure Summary 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Fall Orientation 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid Cuts 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Flyers 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Food Co-op Survey 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Food Service Contract nd (Box 12)
  - Food Services 1980-1981 (Box 12)
  - Food Services 1983 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1983 (Box 12)
  - Fraternity Rush Proposal 1983 (Box 12)
  - Fundraising n.d. (Box 12)
  - Gay and Lesbian Concerns 1992 (Box 12)
  - Gay Student Union (GSU) (Status Change) 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Greek Concerns--Inter-Fraternity Council 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - Guest Speakers at Student Council Meetings 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Handicapped Concerns Committee 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Halloween Fest 1988-1991 (Box 12)
  - Honor Committee 1980 (Box 12)
  - Hook Book (Advertising) 1980-1988, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Housing 1972-1977 (Box 13)
  - Hunger Issues 1985 (Box 13)
  - Inauguration 1985 (Box 13)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Intramural Sports 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Invoices 1989-1992 (Box 13)
  - Judiciary Committee--Student Legal Defense Fund 1979-1983 (Box 13)
  - Landlord/Tenant Legislation 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Lawn Resident Selection 1980-1992 (Box 13)
  - Lawn Use Policy 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Leadership Program--Summer 1991 (Box 13)
  - Legislative Committee--General 1980-1982 (Box 14)
  - Legislative Committee--Correspondence 1979-1986 (Box 14)
  - Lesbian-Gay Student Concerns Committee 1989 (Box 14)
  - Madison House 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Madison House 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Madison House 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Madison House--Board of Directors Manual 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Mascot--Grizzle 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Media Board 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Media Contact--Addresses 1980 (Box 14)
  - Mid-Year Report 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous 1978-1995, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Morgan, Andre--Membership on Committees 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Multicultural Affairs Council 1991 (Box 15)
  - Neighborhood Associations 1989 (Box 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1980-1986 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Arms Lobby 1984 (Box 15)
  - Office Hours n.d. (Box 15)
  - Office Hours 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - Office of Afro-American Affairs 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Office of Governmental Relations 1992 (Box 15)
  - Office of Major Events 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Office Space Allocations 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Parking and Transportation 1980-1987 (Box 15)
  - Parking and Transportation 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Parking and Transportation Committee 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Parking Permit Rates and Fines 1990 (Box 15)
  - Parliamentary Procedure for UVA Student Council n.d. (Box 16)
  - Party Regulations 1988 (Box 16)
  - Pavilion VIII Renovations 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Pep Band 1992 (Box 16)
  - Presidential Advisory Committee 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - President's Retreat 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Press Release 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Printed Material 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Procedures and Policies 1991 (Box 16)
  - Proposed Zoning Ordinance 1984 (Box 16)
  - Publications--Intercollegiate 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Publications--Intercollegiate Press Bulletin (ICPB) 1985 (Box 16)
  - Publicity 1991 (Box 16)
  - Publicity Committee n.d. (Box 16)
  - Race Relations 1991 (Box 16)
  - Rape Commission 1984 (Box 16)
  - Rape Task Force 1984 (Box 16)
  - Rape Task Force 1986 (Box 16)
  - Reagan's Proposed Education Budget Cuts 1985 (Box 16)
  - Receipts 1987 (Box 16)
  - Recognized Organizations 1982-1985 (Box 16)
  - Recruitment and Retention of Black Faculty and Students 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Recycling Committee 1982-1986 (Box 16)
  - Recycling Committee 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Registrar 1980 (Box 16)
  - Registration Table--Fall 1990 (Box 16)
  - Report and Proposals for Continued Improvement in Virginia Higher Education 1988-1991 (Box 16)
  - Report on Residential Colleges 1991 (Box 16)
  - Reports--Miscellaneous 1987-1989 (Box 17)
  - Representatives 1991 (Box 17)
  - Reservations for University Facilities 1991 (Box 17)
  - Residential Colleges--Ad Hoc Committee 1991 (Box 17)
  - Residential Life Committee 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Resolutions 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Retreat Packet 1987 (Box 17)
  - Retreat--Student Council 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Restructure Proposal 1990 (Box 17)
  - Room Reservations 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Safety and Security 1985-1986 (Box 17)
  - Safety Concerns 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Safety Concerns--Deadbolt Lock Issue 1988 (Box 17)
  - Scholarship Committee 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Secretary--Treasurer's Report 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Semester Reports 1985-1990 (Box 17)
  - Sexual Assault 1991-1992 (Box 17)
  - Sexuality Survey 1989 (Box 17)
  - Sharing Charlottesville 1987 (Box 17)
  - Sharing Charlottesville 1989 (Box 17)
  - Sharing Charlottesville 1991 (Box 18)
  - Sharing Charlottesville 1992 (Box 18)
  - Social Activity--Easters 1975-1983 (Box 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference 1991 (Box 18)
  - Southern Regional Student Association 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Southern Regional Student Association 1984 (Box 18)
  - Space Allocations 1983-1986 (Box 18)
  - Space Allocations 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - Speakers 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - Spring Retreat 1992 (Box 18)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities Committee 1983-1986 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities Committee 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities Fee (SAF) 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Student Activity Fee (SAF) 1988 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities Fee (SAF)--Effectiveness Report 1989 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities Fee (SAF)--Treasurer's Manual 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Student Association of Virginia (SAV) 1991 (Box 19)
  - Student Association of Virginia 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Student Bookstore 1984 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Brochures nd (Box 19)
  - Student Council Budget 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Budget 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Budget 1986-1989 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Budget 1989-1991 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Budget Information 1991-1993 (Box 19)
  - Student Council By-laws 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Campaign Ads 1987 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Committee Applications nd (Box 19)
  - Student Council Constitution 1989 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Elections 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Elections 1990 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Elections 1992 (Box 19)
  - Student Council Forum on Tenure at the University of Virginia 1986 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Membership 1983-1990 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Orientation 1980-1985 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Resolutions 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Retreat 1989 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Scholarships 1984-1995 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Secretary 1992 (Box 20)
  - Student Council Year End Report 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - Student Council's Academic Advising Report 1988 (Box 20)
  - Student Discount Card 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - Student Government Association Conference 1988 (Box 20)
  - Student Health Building 1981-1984 (Box 20)
  - Student Health Committee 1979-1986, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Student Health Insurance 1967-1992 (Box 21)
  - Student Health Insurance 1984-1987 (Box 21)
  - Student Health Supplement 1984 (Box 21)
  - Student Leaders 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - Student Leadership Forum 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Student Leadership Workshop 1983 (Box 21)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1979-1983 (Box 21)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1982-1986 (Box 21)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Student Legal Services (SLS) 1991 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1979-1981 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1983 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1984-1987 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1985-1986 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV) 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV)--Letters of Support from Other States 1980 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV)--Reports from Other Sources 1974-1979 (Box 22)
  - Student on the Board of Visitors (BOV)--Selection of the University President 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Student Organization Information 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Student Town Meeting 1986 (Box 22)
  - Summer Addresses 1989 (Box 22)
  - Summer Mailout 1987 (Box 22)
  - Summer Mailout 1989 (Box 22)
  - Supersound--Rape Awareness 1973-1982 (Box 23)
  - Task Force on Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on College Campuses 1991 (Box 23)
  - Teaching Assistants Report 1989 (Box 23)
  - Ten Year Plan Draft 1991 (Box 23)
  - Tenure 1985-1987 (Box 23)
  - Tenure Committee 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Tenure Forum 1986 (Box 23)
  - Towing and Impoundment Lot 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Towing Policy 1985-1986 (Box 23)
  - Treasurer 1981 (Box 23)
  - Trustees 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Tuition and Loan Information 1972-1984 (Box 23)
  - Tuition and University of Virginia Budget 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Tuition Information 1991-1992 (Box 23)
  - Typewriter--IBM Electronic 1985 (Box 23)
  - Undergraduate Academic Review 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - United States Student Association (USSA) 1992 (Box 23)
  - United Way 1983 (Box 23)
  - University Assessment Program 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - University Budget 1983-1987 (Box 24)
  - University Budget Cuts 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - University Committees 1987-1990 (Box 24)
  - University Corner Streetscape Study 1990 (Box 24)
  - University News Office 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - University Relations 1991-1992 (Box 24)
  - University Union 1983-1984 (Box 24)
  - Venable Neighborhood Association 1986 (Box 24)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs 1983-1985 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Association of College Student Government 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Collegiate Services, Inc. 1980 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Discovery Museum Donation 1987 (Box 24)
  - Virginia General Assembly--General 1981-1992, (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Virginia General Assembly--Lobbying 1973-1991, (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Virginia Student Association (VASA) 1981-1985 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Student Association (VASA) 1983-1986 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Student Association (VASA) --Forum 1984 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Student Association (VASA) --Meeting 1979-1985 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Tech Conference 1984 (Box 26)
  - Voter Information Handbook 1984 (Box 26)
  - Voter Registration 1984 (Box 26)
  - Voter Registration 1992 (Box 26)
  - Voter Registration Legislation 1985 (Box 26)
  - Washington Hall 1983 (Box 26)
  - West Main Street Corner Study nd (Box 26)
  - Women's Concerns 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Women's Concerns Coordinator 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Year End Report 1987-1988 (Box 26)
  - Year End Report 1989-1990 (Box 26)
- Women's Concerns
  - Appropriations and Finances 1989 (Box 26)
  - Black History Month 1989 (Box 26)
  - Careers--Women 1976-1978 (Box 26)
  - Contact Groups 1983-1990 (Box 26)
  - Contacts--Sexual Assault 1989 (Box 26)
  - Contracted Independent Organizations (CIO) 1991-1992 (Box 26)
  - Coordinating Council--Charlotesville/Albermarle 1977 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence--Eileen Smith 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Correspondence--Rita O'Donnell 1977-1983 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence--Women's Concerns Committee 1988-1989 (Box 26)
  - Council of Black Student Leaders 1991 (Box 26)
  - Date and Acquaintance Rape Committee 1986, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Date and Acquaintance Rape Month 1989 (Box 26)
  - Education 1972 (Box 26)
  - Equal Opportunity 1977 (Box 26)
  - Equal Rights Amendment 1978 (Box 26)
  - Evaluating a School District's Employment 1978 (Box 26)
  - History of Women's Concerns at the University of Virginia 1977-1979 (Box 26)
  - IRIS 1988 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous--Women's Committee 1989 (Box 28)
  - Multicultural Seminar 1989 (Box 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1974-1989 (Box 28)
  - Permanent Committees--Women's Concerns 1989 (Box 28)
  - Racial Policy 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Rape Awareness Committee 1986 (Box 28)
  - Rape--Fraternities (Frats) 1975-1983 (Box 28)
  - Resources 1973-1978 (Box 28)
  - Safety Concerns 1987-1989 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Assault 1991-1992 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Assault Education Month 1989 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Assault Pamphlets 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Assault Services Coordinator 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Assault Task Force 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Discrimination Legislation 1975-1979 (Box 28)
  - Sexual Harassment 1989 (Box 28)
  - Smith, Eileen Papers 1991-1993 (Box 28)
  - Speakers 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Student Action 1989 (Box 30)
  - Student Council 1989-1990 (Box 30)
  - Student Health--AIDS, Pregnancy, Birth Control 1989 (Box 30)
  - Task Force on the Status of Women at the University of Virginia 1974-1987 (Box 30)
  - Task Force on the Status of Women at the University of Virginia 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Title Nine (Sports) 1979 (Box 30)
  - Vandalism 1977-1978 (Box 30)
  - Women and the Faculty 1974-1978 (Box 30)
  - Women's Center 1984-1988, (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Women's Concerns Committee 1986-1989 (Box 30)
  - Women's Concerns Committee 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Women's Literature 1988 (Box 31)
  - Women's Sports 1979 (Box 31)
  - Women's Studies 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Women's Week 1990 (Box 31)
- Gay and Lesbian Concerns
  - About Face Conference Briefing Book 1990 (Box 31)
  - Agenda and Mission Statement 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - AIDS Awareness Week 1987 (Box 31)
  - AIDS Quilt 1991 (Box 31)
  - Committee Correspondence--General 1979-1993, (fix folder) (Box 31)
  - Comprehensive Study Working Group 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Domestic Partners in Family Housing 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Gay Awareness Week 1987-1989 (Box 31)
  - Gay-Bashing on Downtown Mall 1992 (Box 31)
  - Gay-Bashing Flyers 1988 (Box 31)
  - Gay and Lesbian Freedom March 1992 (Box 31)
  - Gays in the Military--Joe Steffan Speech 1991 (Box 32)
  - Internal Committee Documents 1990-1191 (Box 32)
  - Law School Military Recruitment Ban 1991 (Box 32)
  - Lesbian and Gay Concerns 1991-1992 (Box 32)
  - March on Washington 1987-1993, (2 folders) (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - Mr. Jefferson's Gay Student Journal--Gay Student Union Publication 1972 (Box 32)
  - National Coming Out Day 1990 (Box 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings--Miscellaneous 1988-1993, (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Non-Discrimination Policy Activity 1987-1988 (Box 32)
  - Non-Discrimination Policy--Correspondence 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Parents-Friends of Lesbians and Gays Information 1981 (Box 33)
  - Press Clippings--Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1990-1993 (Box 33)
  - Press Clippings 1988-1993 (Box 33)
  - Proud to Be Out Week 1988, 1990 (Box 33)
  - ROTC--National Day of Action 1991 (Box 33)
  - Rutgers Comprehensive Report on Status of Lesbians/Bisexuals/Gays 1989 (Box 33)
  - STAND Campaign--Response to Racist, Phobic graffiti, includes photographs of graffiti 1990 (Box 33)